<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="https://luc2023fall.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/ignatiusx2/IgX_Cityscape_XSL4_IdEd_Styling3.xsl"?>
<Portfolio>
    <Ideaboxes>
        <Ideabox id="1700443300">
            <Boxname>Uncurated Box</Boxname>
            <Boxlevel_Metadata>BoxMeta</Boxlevel_Metadata>
            <Ideas>
                <Idea id="1700443301">Influence of extracurricular activities on acceptance rates - correlation strength?
                    <Keycat>Admissions Analytics</Keycat>
                </Idea>
                <Idea id="1700443302">Tailoring campus visit experiences using CRM data - possible personalized itineraries?</Idea>
                <Idea id="1700443303">Survey data on prospect priorities - can we map against current touchpoints?</Idea>
                <Idea id="1700443304">Sentiment trends in application essays - indicators of commitment and success post-admission?</Idea>
                <Idea id="1700443305">Historical data vs. current applicant pool - can we refine predictive models for yield rates?</Idea>
                <Idea id="1701482298301">testytest</Idea>
                <Idea id="1701482483133">Impact of application timing on acceptance - early birds vs. regular.</Idea>
                <Idea id="1701482517652">Geographic trends in admissions data - urban vs. rural success rates.</Idea>
                <Idea id="1701482530916">Geographic trends in admissions data - urban vs. rural success rates.</Idea>
            
			     <Idea id="1701482990606">GOOFY. Give out free potatoes with the school's name on them. </Idea>
		      
			<Idea id="1701483071107">Keyword is amazingness of the data, super duper lovely!</Idea>
		
			<Idea id="1701483101524">I love new ideas and I love making new ideas!</Idea>
		
			<Idea id="1701483265056">Meanwhile, back at the ranch, Lassie was saving the town yet again.</Idea>		
			<Idea id="1701483322055">The quick brown fox jumped over the lazy dog to get to the pizza.
</Idea>		
			<Idea id="1701483366119">The pizza was both amazing and delicious.
</Idea>	
			<Idea id="1701483379900">The delicious pizza won awards at various food events.</Idea>	
			<Idea id="1701483656349">teserserserserserser</Idea>
			<Idea id="1701483661086">weqweqweqweqweqweqweqweqw</Idea><Idea id="1701485403011">test<Keycat>testttestesetset</Keycat></Idea>
			<Idea id="1701485505660">The quick pizza jumped over the amazing brown dog.
				<Keycat>Pizza Stories</Keycat>
			</Idea>
			<Idea id="1701485527368">The pepperoni was analytical and met all cybersecurity requirements.
				<Keycat>Cyber Pepperoni</Keycat>
			</Idea>
			<Idea id="1701485995524">The cyber-pepperoni could go well with cyber-anchovies.
				<Keycat>Cyber Pepperoni</Keycat>
			</Idea>
			<Idea id="1701486185316">The cyber anchovies are able to use John the Ripper to crack passcodes.
				<Keycat>Cyber Pepperoni</Keycat>
			</Idea>
			<Idea id="1701486344595">The passcodes include those from the Rockyou list, oh my.
				<Keycat>Cyber Pepperoni</Keycat>
			</Idea>
			<Idea id="1701486510259">Passcode pepperoni cheese and sausage
				<Keycat>Cyberpizza</Keycat>
			    <TimestampCreated/>
			</Idea>
			<Idea id="1701486857623">Cyber pepperoni is amazing stuff, we love it.
				<Keycat>Cyberpizza</Keycat>
				<TimestampCreated>12/02/2023 04:14:17</TimestampCreated>
			</Idea>
			<Idea id="1701487288253">The superb pizza wins the security prize for its amazingness. 
				<Keycat>Cyberpizza</Keycat>
				<TimestampCreated>12/02/2023 04:21:28</TimestampCreated>
			</Idea>
			<Idea id="1701490272188">This quick brown fox is having pizza and a few cocktails using our cocktail API!</Idea>
			<Idea id="1701490478170">The pizza flying above the city hovered, waiting for its time to enjoy a good beer.
				<Keycat/>
				<TimestampCreated>12/02/2023 05:14:38</TimestampCreated>
			</Idea>
			<Idea id="1701561236131">The tasty pizza was well-fired up in a tasty hot stone oven.
				<Keycat/>
				<TimestampCreated>12/03/2023 00:53:56</TimestampCreated>
			</Idea>
			<Idea id="1701561297070">The tasty pizza in the hot stone oven was covered in pepperoni.
				<Keycat>Cyberpizza</Keycat>
				<TimestampCreated>12/03/2023 00:54:57</TimestampCreated>
			</Idea></Ideas>
        </Ideabox>
    </Ideaboxes>
</Portfolio>
